crictime.is 2018-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Crictime.is

**Privacy Policy**

This is the privacy policy of web site Crictime.is

We can be reached via feedback given on the website.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes information of   
your browser, IP address, City/State/Country.

We do not collect the e-mail address of visitors to our Web pages except the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail.

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor.

**With respect to Ad Servers:** To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

Crictime.is has no access to or control over these cookies/Web beacons that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Crictime.is privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through third-party advertising networks, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using that advertising network. This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above email address.
